<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Alzheimer\'s Awareness Quiz</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome to the \nAlzheimer\'s Awareness Quiz!</string>
    <string name="instructions">You will be asked 10 questions about the signs and symptoms of alzheimer\'s disease.
        \nAnswer each question to the best of your knowledge. \nYour responses will be scored at the end.
    </string>
    <string name="description">
        DISCLAIMER
        \nThis app was created to raise awareness and direct those that believe they or their loved one may be
        suffering from the early stages of alzheimer\'s disease to more information from the Alzheimer\'s Association.
        This quiz does not diagnose or treat any illness and is not endorsed by any medical professional or the Alzheimer\'s Association.
        Materials from alz.org are used with permission by the Alzheimer's Association.
    </string>
    <string name="editName">First Name (optional)</string>
    <string name="userName">Hello, </string>
    <string name="continueButton">Submit Name</string>
    <string name="logoDescription">Logo of Alzheimer\'s Association</string>
    <string name="q1">Question 1</string>
    <string name="q1text">Do you or your love one experience any of these examples of memory loss that disrupt daily life? Check all that apply:</string>
    <string name="q1example1">Forgets recently learned information.</string>
    <string name="q1example2">Forgets important dates or events.</string>
    <string name="q1example3">Asks for the same information over and over.</string>
    <string name="q1example4">Increased need to rely on memory aids or family members for things once handled by self.</string>
    <string name="q1AgeRelated">Sometimes forgetting names or appointments, but remembering them later can be an age-related change.</string>
    <string name="noneResponse">None of these.</string>
    <string name="toastScroll">Scroll down to reveal first question.</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit Answer</string>
    <string name="q2">Question 2</string>
    <string name="q2text">Do you or your loved one experience challenges in planning or solving problems? Check all that apply.</string>
    <string name="q2example1">Changes in your/their ability to develop and follow a plan.</string>
    <string name="q2example2">Changes in your/their ability to work with numbers.</string>
    <string name="q2example3">Have trouble following a familiar recipe or keeping track of monthly bills.</string>
    <string name="q2example4">Difficulty concentrating and taking much longer to do things than you/they did before.</string>
    <string name="q2AgeRelated">Making occasional errors when balancing a checkbook can be an age-related change.</string>
    <string name="q3">Question 3</string>
</resources>
